mondovo.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy | Mondovo.com

### Overview

www.mondovo.com is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who directly or indirectly use the website.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which our suite of SEO tools, social tools, analytics tools collects, uses, maintains and discloses information obtained from users of the www.mondovo.com website. This privacy policy applies to this website and all its offerings.

### Personal identification information

www.mondovo.com might have to collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways––including, but not limited to, when the users visit this site, place an order, fill out a form. These terms also apply in connection with all the other services, features or resources available on the site. The users of this site might be requested, where applicable, to disclose their name, email address and other details. The personal identification information would be collected from users only if they voluntarily decide to submit the same.Non-personal identification information implies details like browser name, type of computer, operating system and Internet service provider name.

### Identification information (Non-personal)

www.mondovo.com might at times collect non-personal identification information of users in order to offer the privilege of accessing some parts of the site for availing some of the services. Non-personal identification information implies details like browser name, type of computer, operating system and Internet service provider name are also within the ambit of non-personal identification information.

### Browser cookies

www.mondovo.com uses cookies to recognize users and maximize user experience. Whenever a user visits the site, their web browser places cookies on the drive for activity tracking/ record keeping. The user has all the liberty to refuse these cookies or get an alert when these cookies are being sent. This can be done through the browser settings. If cookies are blocked, the website www.mondovo.com, or some parts of it, may not function as expected. We also may not be able to offer some of the services you had signed up for. 

### Using collected information

Our SEO, social, analytics tool set may collect and use personal information for the below furnished reasons.

  * To identify you as a user of www.mondovo.com
  * To improve customer service by addressing queries more effectively
  * To personalize user experience
  * To improve our website and services
  * To collect feedback from you
  * To run a promotion, contest or survey 
  * To send useful information/updates users have agreed to receive
  * To send periodic order/service/query related emails

If at any time the user wishes to unsubscribe from receiving communication, he/she may do so. We include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Protecting your information

At www.mondovo.com, we deploy appropriate information gathering, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information stored on our website.

Sensitive and private data exchange between our website and its users happens over an SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Sharing your personal information

At www.mondovo.com, we do not sell or rent our users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business on our behalf. Third party tools for sending out emailers is a case in point. We may share your information with these third parties for limited purposes, if you have given us permission.

Additional Limits on Use of Your Google User Data: Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, if you provide the App access to the following types of your Google data, the App's use of that data will be subject to these additional restrictions:

The App will only use access to read and analyze your Google Analytics and Google Search Console data and will not transfer this data to others unless doing so is necessary to provide and improve these features, comply with applicable law, or as part of a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets. The App will not use this data for serving advertisements. The App will not allow any other third party to read this data unless we have your affirmative agreement for specific messages, doing so is necessary for security purposes such as investigating abuse, to comply with applicable law, or for the App's internal operations and even then only when the data have been aggregated and anonymized.

### Changes to this privacy policy

www.mondovo.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time without notifying you. We encourage our users to frequent this page to check for any changes and to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You hereby acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

As a member/user of www.mondovo.com, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you disagree fully or partly to this policy, please do not use our site/services. Your continued use of the website following the changes will be considered as acceptance of all the terms and conditions in the privacy policy.

Should you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy of www.mondovo.com, please contact us with your concerns.

Our website has been operational from 2014. Learn more [about us](https://www.mondovo.com/about-us.php) and [what does Mondovo mean?](https://www.mondovo.com/about-us.php)
